Today we're going to talk about what's
working right now to get clients in your
business that are going to pay you
money. And this is going to be a kind of
a mini master class that you can take
with you, take lots of notes to be able
to apply to build your business. If
you're a coach, a course creator, you're
building a program, the reason why
you're doing it, of course, is for the
impact that it's going to have and you
do so ethically and you want to help
people. uh but we wouldn't be doing it
if it wasn't a viable way to make money
that we knew was possible to do. So, and
we see all these things like, oh, you
can make a h 100,000 here, you can make
200,000 here, you can do all that. But
what does it really take to actually get
to that level? Well, the number one
thing that is missing
is this.
It's trust.
Because
when you go out there to market your
courses or your coaching program, there
are so many different courses and
coaching programs out there. People
don't trust that you are going to be the
answer to what they're looking for. No
matter how good it is. How do I know
this? because I I'm personally biased by
this, but my clients also do say this
that they'll they can comment below as
well uh on this and and I didn't pay
them to say any of this, but
we have one of the best coaching
programs on the planet when it comes to
getting results, showing you the
process, working through the mindset,
and showing you exactly what it takes to
be able to get clients. I've been doing
this business in this industry for over
22 years, almost 23 years.
And yet, people don't trust me. Not
because I did anything wrong, but
because of the industry, because
they're not going to trust anybody.
People will not trust that you can
deliver simply because you have
something valuable. So, you have to
actually build that trust with people.
And there's a process for doing so uh in
people's minds. Number one, like videos
like this are used to build trust. Your
content is used to build trust. Your
email list. And so oftentimes we look at
those things as like those are our
marketing and our advertising avenues
and all those things when in fact they
also serve a dual purpose. Not just to
reach new people. Like this is the first
video you're watching with me. That's
great. But that's not going to just
build enough trust that you're now going
to become a a VIP client of mine and
we're going to be working one-on-one
together and we're going to be building
your business together to tomorrow. I
mean, that would be great. If you want
to do that, reach out. I I'm open for
it. I'm here for it. I'd love to work
with you on that.
But trust
is something that goes on in the mind of
your prospect where they believe that
you are the answer to the problem that
they have. they have a problem. They're
struggling with something. They're not
getting the result they want and they
want a change. Okay? So, that's if
you're a coach, if you're a mentor, if
you're a service provider, they have a
problem and you are going to do the
service that's going to make the change.
Both of those, by the way, share a lot
of similarities. And the methodology is
getting clients is pretty much the same
between the two. Uh it's just what are
you selling is going to be a little bit
different. what's the offer that you're
making to people. By the way, most of
the time, most coaching offers can have
a high-end service aspect to it. When
you're building your business, you want
to have a value ladder where you have
low cost, low ticket, mid, high ticket.
You know,
we have a brand new course that just
came out. It's five bucks. It's all
about uh Instagram ads. What's working
for Instagram ads? the latest cutting
edge strategies of building successful
Instagram ad campaigns and it's it's
been selling like crazy and we have a
mid-t
wealthy coach academy program. It's it's
honestly what most people offer in their
high ticket programs. We're offering it
in a midt
uh starts at $77 for the first month for
most people. They can even get 14 days
free through certain promotions that we
offer.
um it's $197 a month if they continue
and we have a lot of people who stay
with us for years at that rate uh which
is amazing and that's our mid level
right there and then our high ticket is
my VIP program where I give you
one-on-one
I work with you come alongside you
personally one-on-one to be able to
build that with you and that's
phenomenal the results that we get from
that I also have a consulting level
that's above that that most people it's
way way too expensive for most people
mostly just for seven figure uh earners
that I work with people that are making
seven figures on that level. Uh on the
beginning level I work with people that
are just getting started and that's what
these videos are for. That's what my $5
courses are for. That's what my Wealthy
Coach Academy is for. Um, and so but for
anybody to become a client of those, for
anybody to even purchase my $ five
dollar Instagram ads course, right?
There's a ton of Instagram ads courses
that are out there. It takes me building
trust with people to believe that I can
deliver on what I say. And by the way,
it has nothing to do with my lip service
or anything like that. It's when you can
combine two things. Trust is built on
emotion
and logic
coming together.
They end up linking together to where it
both feels right and the details are
there. If you're just leading with the
logical details of why you can help
somebody and it feels off, which by the
way, this is what most people are end up
doing. Most coaches that I meet,
they check all the boxes of the logic
side of things. Most of the ones who I
work with. They like they have
incredible products, but they just that
something feels off about working with
them. Something doesn't feel right is is
this side of it. And I've also met some
people where they got the feeling side
of things great, but they're not
actually delivering on the logic side.
It's a little bit too feely feely. So,
both of those need to be together. You
got to deliver results and it has to
feel right. It has to feel like, okay,
this person's going to be able to do the
thing that they want to do. Now, how do
you actually build that trust? Well, we
use certain mechanisms. Again, like I
said, the mechanical side of it, videos
like this, our email list, we have our
our $5 courses, we have our our midt
program, we have our our all those
different programs build trust for the
next level. people that are in the $5
trainings, people who watch these
YouTube videos. It's to build trust for
the Wealthy Coach Academy program. Once
somebody's in the Wealthy Coach Academy
program, I'm going to serve them at the
highest level to build trust for my VIP
one-on-one program. And so with that,
it's got to make sense to somebody.
That's those are the mechanical sides of
things. Now, how do you actually deliver
that trust? Well, what you have to do is
you have to go higher and you have to
understand
what is the pain
and pleasure
that the prospect is looking to avoid
and experience.
And what this really boils down to is
their deepest
desire. Understanding their deepest
desire. What are they wanting more than
anything else?
And so when you know what their deepest
desire is and then you promise that
desire,
okay, what that does is that is going to
touch the logical side of things right
here. We end up promising that desire.
When we start to communicate in a way
that shows that we understand and feel
their pain,
that builds trust. That's master
communication.
Not that you're amplifying the pain, but
you show that you can feel it. And then
we also want people to realize that the
pleasure that they're looking for, they
are not going to experience that
unless they start working with you.
And so like the idea is is that listen,
if somebody goes on to build their
business on their own and they spend all
this time to build it on their own, they
are going to suffer.
And if they work with me, that suffering
is going to disappear.
And so they can continue to suffer
on their own. And maybe and and and
unfortunately, they're going to probably
go through coaching program after
coaching program after coaching program
that is not going to serve them, that is
not going to deliver results, that is
not going to help them when they could
have saved all that pain and suffering
by working with me in my program. And
and and that's the truth.
Now, me just simply saying that is not
nearly enough to build trust with
people. Okay?
But it piques people's curiosity because
I have conviction in that. I have belief
in that. We have testimonies that say
it. We have clients that say it. We have
people who reiterate that.
Again, you can see them in the comments
below. They'll comment. I know they
will, you know, about how great it is
working with us.
But with this,
what ends up happening is
you're not going to get clients
until you start to build everything in
your business around that desire that
people have. So what you want to do is
then you want to start crafting your
content, your podcast, your webinars,
your program, the hook as to why people
are signing up around what is that
desire that they have. What is the pain
that they're looking to move away from?
What is the pleasure that they're
looking to move towards to show that you
understand? To show that you truly care.
And then what we do is we get real
specific.
we get really
specific about what those details are.
This is like five layers deep specific.
Okay? And what you'll do is you'll take
one pillar or two pillars of how you
help people
and you'll break that down in some kind
of a miniourse. You'll break it down in
video content like this.
So, like in my program, I give all of
the stuff from hiring people to um
writing emails to using AI on an expert
level. I'm one of the best at using AI
to automate a lot of the stuff that we
do. A lot of the stuff we don't have to
work so hard because the AI can help us.
But you got to get specific
in your offer and not try to offer
everything. You don't want to fire hose
everybody with everything. This is one
of the biggest issues that I see a lot
of coaches and mentors make is that
they're trying to give so much of the
right information, the right value
that they literally will not reach the
people that they're trying to reach
because they're trying to
serve at such a high level.
And they think that that's what's going
to build trust with people and it's not.
And this is the this is the part where
people get wrong. And this is the sauce.
This is the secret sauce. Like like if
you're looking for a secret sauce
in this YouTube video right here, this
is it.
is you could have the best program, the
best information, share all the best
stuff,
but if you're trying to
focus on checking all the boxes
and give people all the right
information
and you don't specifically point out not
every problem they have, but just one
problem
and one key solution.
So we focus on one problem,
one solution.
Inside of my wealthy coach academy
program,
I show people
all of the different aspects of building
a successful coaching business. all of
the different aspects of what it takes
to experience the kind of results that
they're looking for to have the kind of
breakthroughs that they're hoping for.
But when I'm marketing, when I'm making
YouTube videos, when I'm making content,
I'm only dealing with a specific aspect.
Why do course creators struggle to get
their content out? How can people that
use Instagram ads make sure that their
ads convert better? How do you create
better ads? How do you create better
offers? Those are three separate pillars
right there. Three separate problems,
three separate solutions that inside of
my coaching program I cover with
different courses and trainings and I
can answer those different questions.
But when it comes to
when it comes to your marketing to get
clients and that trust building
exercise,
focus on just one of those aspects
and really dial it in
and go dial it home with people as to
what one of those aspects are.
So, for instance, I talk a lot about
Instagram ads and how to create them and
how to use AI to make ads and how the AI
can help you write the ads and generate
them and all that. And again, that's
what that $5 course is all about. You
can find that in the description.
So, we're going to focus on one key
problem. I'm I'm going to make a another
$5 course here on
using AI to make videos for your
content. We've been doing that a lot.
How to create irresistible offers. Those
are key problems, key solutions that are
used as an entry point into your world,
into your ecosystem.
And so that singular entry point
is where people are coming in with that
one key problem, one key solution. And
so if you're trying to reach people
with all of these different things and
you're not getting specific enough,
you're going to miss it.
And so that's what you want to do. And
then you want to build an offer around
that. You want to write it. Create your
sales letter. Create your your training.
Reach people with that. Amplify it out
with ads to reach as many people as
possible.
Sell it. And then use that to upgrade
and to ascend people into your paid
programs. And that's that's the process
of getting clients. That's the process
of building trust.
And maybe it doesn't happen right away.
Maybe it doesn't happen in one instance,
but it happens in the long term and it
happens over time by connecting with
people around those things. And so if
you can do that, if you can start to
connect with people and get real
specific around one key problem, one key
solution, and you start to deliver that
in a paid webinar format,
you can then start to sell that to
people, use it to build trust, use it to
sell your programs
and get more clients. I think in a
future video I'm going to make where I
do the blueprint of what to actually say
in one of those webinars. I think that'd
be a great idea. I'd love to see you
join us in one of our trainings and I'd
love to see you join me in the Wealthy
Coach Academy program. Click the link
below
and let's work together. We'll talk
soon. Have a good one.